You've had your nose
in that book for the last 10 miles.
What was the name of that redheaded
security guard at the, uh, bioresearch lab?
Hardin?
- H-Harken.
- Harken. Harken. Yes, that's it. Thank you.
I hate to be a buzzkill, Jane but even if you
could remember everybody you've ever met
what if Lorelei Martins
is lying?
What if you've never
actually met Red John?
I haven't just met him.
I've shaken hands with him.
And she wasn't lying.
She didn't realize what she told me.
- Am I in that book?
- No.
she said it's a wonder
Red John and I didn't become friends.
Now what we have,
I consider a friendship.
So, my friend,
you are free and clear.
That's a relief.
- Hey. Are you in charge here?
- Uh, yeah, sure.
Listen, I've been here
for several hours now.
I'm a busy man.
When can I leave?
Uh, I don't know.
Who are you?
Chip McGavin. I found the body.
I told the officers what I saw.
They said I had to stay here
and say it all over again
to you guys
before I could leave.
Is that so?
- Yes, that's so, Chip.
- This is ridiculous.
Let me tell you something, Chip.
I'll give you a heads-up.
You're our number one
suspect right now
so I'd play it cool
if I were you.
We'll be with you
in a moment.
Rigsby.
- What have we got?
- You know what? Quit it.
Well, according to his I.D.,
victim's name's Lemuel McVie.
M.E.'s putting time of death
between 10 and 12 hours ago.
Looks like he was hit multiple times
with some kind of blunt object.
Not dressed for golf.
How did he end up in there?
Well, we found tire tracks
by the water's edge, so...
which means he was murdered
elsewhere and dumped here.
We need to find
the initial murder site.
His life had just begun.
- He's not that young.
- No, his new life. This is a new wallet.
And his driver's license and credit card
were established only two years ago.
- But look at his hands.
- Scarred knuckles.
It's evident that this man
has been in a scrap or two.
- From his old life. Rigsby.
- Yeah. I'm running his license now.
I do like that cufflink.
Very crafty.
Perhaps the other one
was lost in the scuffle.
Why dump him on a golf course?
Ah, this place goes on for acres and acres.
Multiple points of entry.
I don't think there's
any cameras around here.
Seems like the perfect place.
Well, he was busted for marijuana
possession four years ago.
And apparently our victim
is associated
with a street gang
called the 10th Street Ghouls.
- That puts a different spin on it.
- Yo, Chip. Front and center.
I'm starting to resent you.
- Good. You a member of a street gang?
- No, of course not.
- Really? Did you kill this man?
- No, I did not.
Liar. I can see it in your eyes.
Arrest him, Lisbon.
- Wait a minute. You can't do that.
- Yeah, I'm just kidding.
But next time you come across
a dead body, Chip, show a little respect.
- Thank you.
- I'm sorry. Uh, Rigsby...
would you interview Mr. McGavin?
Thank you.
All right, Mr. McGavin...
You know what? You can write
my name down in that book.
- Oh, come on!
- Put me in it. I want to be in it.
No, no. Come on. Really?
Juliana, we're very sorry
about Lemuel.
My brother's name was Lem.
Nobody called him Lemuel.
Uh, excuse me.
Do you have any tea?
- What?
- I'll just take a look in the kitchen.
Excuse me?
Uh, could...could you show me
where the tea is in the kitchen, please?
Thank you.
- So how'd they do it?
- Who do you think did it?
I don't know.
How did they do it?
- He was beaten to death.
- Son of a bitch.
Do you think the 10th Street Ghouls
had anything to do with this?
No, he's been done with them
almost three years now.
Is that when Lem got his driver's license
and established those credit cards?
- Yeah.
- You're sure he was out?
I'm positive. He jumped out as soon
as they tried to recruit Noah.
He wanted to set a better example.
So he got a good job
and he even helped me
pay for nursing school.
Lem stepped up.
He did right by us.
Not a single tea drinker in the family.
That's interesting.
But you do have cocoa.
You want a cup of hot cocoa?
I'm pretty handy with a kettle.
You should trust me.
Nope?
- Where was he working?
- Wintergrove Realty.
- He was a salesman there.
- What about yesterday?
Was there anything that he said
or did that jumps out at you?
No. Just that he didn't
come home last night.
Your parents are gone, aren't they?
You have custody of Noah?
I know what it's like to be the one to keep
the family together. It's a tough job.
Don't make it tougher.
If you know who did this, tell me.
I don't know who did this.
It's tough when you lose somebody.
But you still carry them with you.
I mean, your memories and...
Choices you make in life.
You made him those
cool cufflinks, didn't you?
At school in crafts.
I gave them to Lem
for being promoted.
He said a man should always dress
like the man he wants to be.
- Sounds like a good brother.
- Yeah.
That's a sweet ride
you two have there.
Cherry on cherry.
Lem let me choose the stripes.
Great.
It's got a 4-barrel carburetor,
dual exhaust and Nanobrock intakes.
Get out of here.
Nanobrock intakes.
- You ready to go?
- Sure.
Yeah. Noah was just telling me
about Lem's car.
Was he driving that yesterday?
- You mind if I take a picture?
- No.
Let's go.
Keep your chin up.
Here's the picture
of the victim's missing car.
'68 Olds. Nice.
I put a BOLO out
to surrounding agencies.
I'm also checking impound lots
to see if anything came through.
Was there any sign of the car
at the golf course?
He was dumped
from a different car.
The tracks we found by the water were
from a car with a smaller wheelbase.
Lem McVie's car was pretty distinctive.
Maybe he was carjacked.
They would have just left him
in the middle of the street.
This feels more planned.
Dumping the body out in the open
like that feels like a gang hit.
His sister was adamant that
he was done with that life.
Maybe that life
wasn't done with him.
Go upstairs,
talk to somebody in gangs.
See if they can shine
any light on this.
Rigsby, keep checking his cell phone
and his credit card information.
- Van Pelt, stay on the car.
- No problem.
Jane and I are gonna go
to the real estate agency he worked at.
- Agent Wade.
- Come on in.
So, what do you have
on Lemuel McVie and the Ghouls?
Looks like your guy's dad
helped start the Ghouls.
Got stabbed while serving
a life sentence in Lompoc.
Lem had some clout.
He was selling drugs from at least
a 10-block radius at one point.
Well, you don't get to that kind of position
unless you know how to hustle.
- We heard he jumped out.
- Seems like it.
He hasn't come up in any of our sweeps
for at least a couple years now.
What about gangs that have
a beef with the Ghouls?
- Anybody looking to make a statement?
- No. Nobody.
The Ghouls cleared
everyone out years ago.
Corner shot assault rifle.
I didn't realize gang division
had those kinds of resources.
It's for the new rapid response
team we're creating.
- CBI personnel, SWAT tactics.
- That's a good idea.
- You mind? I haven't seen one in years.
- Go for it.
- You a vet?
- 1st Group, Special Forces. You?
Marines. Better put that thing down
before you shoot someone, doggie.
- Thank you.
- Anytime.
Mr. Dilmer's waiting for you
in his office.
Any interest in doing
a tour of the model homes
- after your business is done?
- Are you serious?
Well, interest rates couldn't be lower.
It's a great time to buy.
- Pass.
- I'd like to take a look.
- You can count me in, Tiffany.
- Great.
Mr. Dilmer?
This is Agent Lisbon from the CBI.
And this is Mr. Jane.
Oh, of course. Nathan Dilmer.
Thanks, Tiffany.
See you later, Mr. Jane.
Uh, before you go, did either of you
see Lem leave last night?
I did. I was heading out
for a mixer
and I saw him leave
at the end of the day.
It, uh, was about 6:30.
- In his car?
- Yes.
Yeah, because when I left around
a little after 7:00 his car was gone.
Well, thank you, Tiffany.
What a tragedy.
I worry about how everyone's coping.
Oh, they're just anxious about
who's gonna get Lem's leads.
That's not how I run my office.
I've worked hard to foster
a cohesive and dynamic community here.
We just got back from our annual
office retreat, in fact.
Lem was family.
Hey. Put another one
on the board for me, Dil.
Oh, yeah. Victor, uh, this is
Agent Lisbon from the CBI.
This is her associate Mr. Jane.
Victor Phipps, my top man.
Uh, poor Lem.
Tragedy. Tragedy.
That champagne must have
a bitter taste to it.
I don't want to argue, Detective.
But it's just a sales prop.
Show must go on.
Victor was Lem's supervisor.
They made an outstanding team.
He was a good kid.
Good salesman.
You saw something in Lem
that you recognized.
Sure.
Uh, because you both had a different
kind of life before real estate
- different kind of jobs?
- That's right.
- You're a... Disbarred lawyer.
- You reading my mail?
No. But you just said
"nolo contendere." Lawyer.
And you wouldn't be working here
if you weren't disbarred. No offense.
Corporate litigation. 14 years. Partner
the last six. I took the rap for a client.
What we were is not who we are.
That's my motto.
We're big on giving people
second chances around here.
So you knew about Lem's
gang situation then?
Well, he came to us through
a program for ex-gang youth.
An office full of second chancers.
And you're the head of the office.
So are you a Saint
or another reformed sinner?
Aren't we here
to talk about Lem?
Well, you strike me as
the consensus-building type
so I'm gonna guess
that your crime was fraud.
Ponzi scheme, perhaps.
I paid back society
for the errors in my judgment.
My mistakes do not define me
moving forward.
Another one.
Can either of you think of anybody
that Lem may have had a problem
with like a coworker, client?
Actually, he did come to work,
uh, a bit banged up... about a month ago?
- I'm sorry. "Banged up"?
- Uh, black eye. Uh, tried to cover it up.
I asked him if he needed any help.
He said that he could handle it.
What do you got?
I got back the preliminary
autopsy report.
Lem was struck with
several different objects.
But the X-rays showed
some older fractures.
One to his ribs couldn't have
been more than a month old.
His boss said he came into work
pretty banged up around a month ago.
Based on that,
I did some digging.
Lem visited the emergency room three times
in the last year for various injuries...
all listed as accidents.
It says here his sister
Juliana signed him out.
- She signed him out every time.
- Why didn't she tell us that?
You don't know where Juliana is
and you haven't heard from her?
She's just out.
You don't have anything else
you want to tell us?
Nothing.
You know, the way
you're clenching your fists
suggests that you do have
something you want to tell us.
We can't talk to you.
Y'all can't do anything.
I know Lem would never want you to be afraid
to look another man in the eye, right?
He told me to stay strong,
no matter what happens.
You are being strong, but,
you know your sister needs help.
Where'd she go?
- Hey! Where's Shade?
- Man...
- Where is he?!
- Is she serious?
Yo, yo, you better get up out of here
with all that, little girl.
You see where you at, right?
Go home, man.
Let's go, guys.
I said, where is Shade?
You think it's funny?
- Police! Drop the weapon now!
- What?
Drop your weapon now!
Put your hands up!
Police, drop your weapon!
Everybody, hands in the air!
Don't move, stay where you are!
- Juliana, put the gun down.
- No!
They were hanging out laughing.
They just killed my brother!
Like it was nothing!
Put it down
so we don't have to use ours.
Juliana... Please.
Put it down and let's talk.
Get away.
Up against the fence.
Go!
Hands up.
Where's Noah? He's never
been alone all night.
Sit down.
Noah's fine.
He spent the night
with your neighbor Yasmin
and we brought him here
this morning.
- Where did you get the gun?
- Lem had it hidden for protection.
You think the Ghouls are behind
Lem's murder. Anyone in particular?
Yeah, this dude named Shade.
Lem used to work corners
for him back in the day.
Is that who fractured
Lem's rib earlier this year?
Shade was hella pissed
when Lem quit.
But he had to take it.
Lem jumped out.
Then he just started going in
hard on Lem this year.
Why now?
Well, Shade wasn't making enough money
selling drugs as he was with Lem
- so he felt like Lem owed him.
- And Lem just let him do it?
Yeah, Lem said eventually
Shade would move on.
And I thought he was right.
- And then Shade came back?
- Yeah. The night Lem died.
Shade came to the house
banging on the door like 8:30
mouthing off about how
Lem was gonna get his.
And I called Lem,
but he never answered his phone.
- Juliana, you should have called the police.
- And told them what?
- That a Ghoul was looking for an ex-Ghoul?
- They could have helped you.
Lady, my mother was shot
in broad daylight.
Three years later, they still
don't know who did it.
Cops? Please. Y'all just show up
to collect the bodies.
Are we done?
I need to get my brother home.
Juliana, you discharged
an unregistered firearm.
- You're gonna be arrested.
- Arrested? Well, what about Noah?
You're not gonna put him
in foster care, are you?
If there's no immediate family that
can take custody, that's what happens.
I'm sorry.
You... You can't do this!
Hey, boss.
Shade's real name...
Jeron Slaughter.
Receiving stolen goods,
armed robbery, and attempted murder.
He's a real charmer.
Well, he's in charge of enforcing
discipline within the Ghouls.
Beats down crew members
when they step out of line.
- Do we have a location on Shade?
- Maybe.
He hangs at one of their stash
houses several times a week.
All right, go and pick him up.
Well, the stash house is fortified...
barred windows, steel doors.
Maybe we could use the new
rapid response team.
Coordinate it.
I need to call Child Services.
You got it.
Hey.
Nobody's telling me what's going on.
Do you know where my sister is?
Yeah. She's... she's just
down the hall. She's okay.
- How are you doing?
- I'm okay.
Hi, Noah.
- Listen. We have a situation...
- you know, Lisbon, I-I have a great idea.
A brilliant idea. Excuse me.
One second. Come here.
What brilliant idea?
Well, um...
There isn't one.
I just don't want you to send
that kid to a foster home.
- I don't have a choice.
- Well, there's always choices.
- Okay, like what?
- Let 'em go home.
You don't have to charge
his sister yet, do you?
Just... Just... just think
about it for a while.
She broke the law. I already called
the D.A. and Child Services.
Just let 'em go home.
Got Lem's phone records.
He had two calls
from a disposable phone
one at 8:15 p.m.
and one at 9:00 p.m.
The call at 9:00
is within our murder window.
Well, that must be our killer.
Try and track down where
the cell phone was sold.
Hey, Rigsby, did they ever find that
other cufflink at the country club?
No. They went through
the water hazard
with a vacuum and a sifter...
came back with nothing.
- Where you goin'?
- Back to Wintergrove.
I have an appointment
to take a look at a model home.
Do you want to come with or are you
gonna stick around and do the right thing?
Jane.
I trust you'll make
the right choice, Lisbon.
Damn you, Jane.
Tell Juliana McVie
she's free to go for now.
Tell her we'll be in touch
about the charges against her.
- Really? But we...
- I know, I know. Just do it, huh?
I gotta go call off
Child Services and the D.A.
Wintergrove in the Woods.
Is this a... company retreat?
- Did you...did you go?
- Up in Carrington? No.
That's strictly for the top salesmen.
I see Lem was there.
Yeah. He was always running
behind the big dogs.
"Big dogs"?
The top salesmen in our company...
Dilmer, Phipps, and Bosh.
- Are you ready for the tour?
- Can't wait.
Tiffany, we, uh... we doing a tour?
Yes. I was just about to take
Mr. Jane to see the models.
She's got pluck, this one.
Honey, I'll take it from here.
Why don't you input
the day's contracts?
- Of course, Mr. Bosh.
- Mr. Jane. Quinton Bosh.
- Bosh. Ah, you're one of the big dogs.
- Well, that's what they tell me.
So, Mr. Jane, what are you
looking for in a home?
Wh-what's that place over there?
- Oh, the Catalina.
- Yeah. That looks interesting.
Well...
I need, uh, large square footage.
4-bedroom, 3 1/2 bathrooms
the place oozes with charm.
Shade's been in there about 40 minutes
so he's nice and tucked in.
"Alpha to Wade.
Three just entered the side of the house."
Copy.
More at the party.
Because of the fortification,
I'm thinking the front door
is the best point of entry.
Cho, you take the two side.
Once we do our thing
- we'll hand him to you.
- Copy that.
Okay, ladies, time to move.
Let's go.
Nickel.
- Yo, get out man!
- CBI! Hands in the air!
Cho, we got a runner.
He's headed your way.
I got him.
Give me your arm.
Get up.
Hey.
You found our victim's car. Well done.
Now, the living room
is the centerpiece
of the Catalina's
4,000-square-foot living area.
And over here we have slab granite
countertops in your gourmet kitchen.
Nice flooring. Very solid.
Yeah. Nothing but upscale
to the max in a Wintergrove home.
Not really feeling it.
You know, I gotta...
I gotta... feel it.
Let's go take a gander
at the other model, shall we?
- The Catalina II?
- Yeah.
Well, it's the exact same layout except
for the extra bedroom and decor theme.
- Sounds good.
- Right.
So this is Catalina II. It's a whopping
4,300 square feet of living space.
- Um, Mr. Jane. Can I help you?
- Uh, Mr. Jane is with me, Phippsy. I got it.
Sure, Bosh.
Um, let me show you the garage.
Ample space for three cars.
Well, as I said living room
is exactly the same.
Well, not exactly. I like it.
Good. Good. Let's take
a look at the extra bedroom.
No. No need.
I'm really feeling it here.
Yeah.
I think I need to be alone
with the house for a moment.
You know, just to check out its aura.
- Aura?
- Yeah.
Well, I'm not gonna buy a house
unless we have compatible auras.
- Of course.
- Ten minutes.
Good. I'll, uh...
I'll be right outside.
Thank you.
- Lisbon?
- "What are you doing?"
Following a hunch.
Uh, you've been following it
for several hours now.
Yeah, well, some take
longer than others.
Playtime's over.
We found Lem's missing car.
Ah. That's excellent. Because I just found
the room where he was murdered.
"Shade."
Tell me how you ended up
with a dead man's car.
- To settle a debt.
- A debt?
Well, he cost me a lot of money
when he jumped out.
I mean, I was cool.
But he started flexing with
a very nice ride this year.
See he obviously forgot
that I made him.
So I'm like, "yo"
"I'm-a need a little more
return on my investment."
Now is this when you
bruised his sternum
or are you talking about
when you fractured his ribs?
"You're funny.
Let's just say he agreed with me."
Up until two nights ago.
Look, I just called to tell him
that I need a little extra.
See, these corners ain't doing
what they should in this economy.
At 8:15 and 9:00 p.m.
on a disposable phone?
Hey, it's cheaper than a plan, man.
Anyway, he tells me go to hell.
He ain't coming off no more cheddar.
And we know you went
to his house to find him.
He wasn't there.
Where'd you go?
- His job.
- You found him at work?
No, his car was parked out in front
of them fake houses so I took it.
And we found evidence that he was killed
in one of those model homes
around the same time
you stole his car.
Now why should I believe
you didn't kill him?
Because that wouldn't be necessary.
See, once I got the car,
I was paid in full.
So Shade stole Lem's car but why does
my gut say he's not the killer?
Well, you have a very smart gut.
And the one thing that
Shade's story does confirm
is that Lem was over at
the model homes after 8:00 p.m.
Long after his coworkers
said he'd left.
Trouble is, anyone can
get into those model homes.
- But what's the motive?
- Still remains to be seen.
I'll put in a request
for CSI at Catalina II.
Hey, boss. I finished
going through Lem's computer.
He recently set up news alerts
for the Carrington Gazette.
Carrington?
Yeah, it's a little town where
they have their company retreat.
According to the browser history
he recently read alerts about burglaries
a missing hunter,
and a house fire?
That's interesting.
Uh, why set up a filter
for a podunk newspaper?
I need Lem's car.
Hold off on that CSI team.
Let's keep the murder site
under wraps for now.
What? Why?
- This is his car, right?
- Definitely.
How'd it get here?
- Should I call the police?
- Yes.
And you better call Dilmer.
- Hey, Sarah.
- Hey.
- How's life as an A.D.A.?
- Ah, I'm enjoying it.
Look, I tried to reach you
before you came down.
We'd like to hold off
on charging Juliana McVie.
- Just a beat.
- Why? It sounds like a dunk.
Ah, this case is still developing
and, you know, we're hoping
to use her against some bigger fish.
- I'd like to have the leverage.
- Okay. But I've read the file.
Don't give her a pass
because she's sympathetic.
She broke the law.
You have statutory duties.
- I hear you. How's Ben?
- He's so wonderful.
Hey, keep me apprised
on McVie.
It was parked here
when we opened the office.
Note was already
on the windshield.
"Bring $50,000 to the place
where you killed Lemuel McVie"
"at 10:30 tonight
or I go to the police at 11:00."
It doesn't make any sense.
This car was stolen
by the killer, wasn't it?
- That's our supposition.
- So what does this mean?
I don't know, Mr. Dilmer.
Someone's playing games, I guess.
Or someone here knows more
than they're telling.
You guys don't have a clue.
I mean, have you even figured
out where Lem was murdered yet?
Thank you for your assistance,
ladies and gentlemen.
You can head on back
to work now.
Like I thought.
You don't know anything.
Okay.
The hook has been baited.
- So now we're breaking and entering?
- Uh, no, 'cause, uh...
I have the key.
Come on.
- It was locked this morning.
- Looked easy.
- No, it's just theft and illegal entry.
- Ladies first.
What makes you so certain
that the killer works at Wintergrove Realty?
Imagine, Lisbon... for a mere 20% down,
all this could be yours.
Fully furnished, lavishly equipped.
- Lacking only one thing.
- What?
Well, isn't it obvious that there should be
a lovely, decorative rug right here
pulling the whole room together?
I mean, the other model had one.
So that's what the killer
used to soak up the blood
- and get the body out of here?
- Precisely.
We should wait in here.
Oh, here. Do you want a drink?
That still doesn't prove that the killer
is a Wintergrove employee.
Well, if it wasn't, why wouldn't they
just leave the body here?
Uh, what's the motive?
Something happened
at the company retreat
- something that...
- What?
Well, we will ask whoever
comes through that front door.
- Down.
- Really?
Come on.
- Hi.
What?
It's okay.
You were talking in your sleep.
- I was?
- And drooling a little.
- W-well, what did I say?
- Well...someone's coming.
- Bosh.
- What?
- That doesn't make sense.
- Why?
He's lazy.
- Hey.
Traffic's crazy out there.
Didn't think I'd make it in time.
Phipps?
He and Bosh hate each other.
- Gentlemen.
- Did you get it?
Yeah, took some doing.
I got it all.
- Cash is in the bag.
- Then I guess we just wait.
- Dilmer?
- The consensus builder.
I don't like this.
I got a bad feeling about this.
Stop your whimpering.
- You got a better idea?
- Screw you!
- Hey, knock it off.
- Screw you, I...
knock it off! Both of you.
We gotta stick together here.
No more squabbling.
Evening, gentlemen.
- What are you doing here?
- Catching killers.
- But the letter...
- He wrote the letter, you idiot!
Ah, you're a quick study there, Phipps.
Quick enough to know
there isn't a law in the land
that's gonna convict us of murder
based off of our compliance
with a vague letter.
That is not entirely true.
- We have motive.
- How do you figure?
You know Lem started reading
the Carrington Gazette
when he came back
from the retreat?
He was particularly interested
in a story about a missing hunter.
But the hunter wasn't
just missing, was he?
He was dead.
- We don't know anything about a hunter.
- Okay.
Yeah. Thanks, Bosh.
- You can go. We'll be in touch.
- What?
Thank you for your assistance.
We can handle this.
Wait. Wait a minute.
You cut a deal?
No, no, no, of course...
I don't know...
I have no idea what
they're talking about.
Then tell me why you get to go!
You really think Bosh is the kind of guy
that's gonna sit around and take the rap
when you two dopes are available?
- Tell me you didn't sell us out.
- No, no, he's messing with you!
Then what did you say?!
What did you say?!
- He's messing with you, jackass!
- Correct.
I was just messing with you.
Lisbon, arrest these clowns.
Put your hands
on your heads now!
The wheelbase and tire pattern of your S.U.V.
match the tracks at the golf course.
- Congratulations.
- Tell me what happened.
It was an accident.
We were up in Carrington
for the retreat.
Dilmer, Phippsy, Lem, and I
were out in the...the woods.
You know, drinking a little,
shooting a little, blowing off steam.
- Did Lem go shooting with you?
- No. Said he used enough guns.
He drank up more than
his share of beers, though.
Then Bosh...
Sees this tree branch move
about 50 yards away.
Thinks it's a deer.
And he starts shooting.
- Hey, shh, shh!
- I know!
Get down!
"And we all start shooting."
Whoo!
- Yeah, baby!
- Whoo!
- All right!
- It's mine!
- I got me a deer!
- I hit it!
Whoo-hoo!
"We go to see what we got."
"It was a man."
"Everyone started
freaking out..."
Lem wanted to go to the police.
It was an accident, he reasoned.
But I know that wasn't a real option.
I'm a lawyer. I know what happens.
We'd be in for years of legal hell
millions in lawyers' fees.
- So Lem agreed to hide the body.
- We all agreed.
- As a team.
- As a family.
It was the best thing
for all of us.
But when we got back,
Lem pulls me aside.
He says he can't go through with it
and he tries to convince me
that we can salvage this thing
if we all just come clean.
He was gonna confess
to the cops.
So I agreed with him.
Told him I needed a little bit of time
to get some things in order.
But instead, you planned how
you were gonna get rid of Lem.
Yes. That night.
"I asked him to open Catalina II"
"to meet with some
late arriving clients."
"It was scud duty
for the junior salesmen"
"so he didn't think anything of it."
"We did it together."
"So that we'd all
be equally guilty."
We were gonna dump him
and the car
but when we got back
out of the house
- the car w... it was gone.
- That's what screwed us.
I still don't understand
what happened.
Who took the car?
"His car was parked out in front
of them fake houses so I took it."
Where'd you guys get it?
You can read about it
in the paper.
Nice digs down here
in Major Crimes.
Agent Wade.
Hey, this is my partner
Wayne Rigsby.
Rigsby, this is Tamsin Wade.
She's heading the new
rapid response team for CBI.
Oh, nice.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Likewise. That's actually why
I came to see you, Cho.
What's up?
I haven't selected an agent
from Major Crimes for the team.
It wouldn't interfere
with your daily duties
and I cleared it
with Agent Lisbon.
So if you're interested,
we'd love to have you on board.
- Sure.
- Great.
Oh, and, uh, end of shift
a few of us are hitting the range
if you want to come join us,
say hi to the team.
I'll see you out there.
- Agent Rigsby.
- Yeah.
Lem's killer has led
the police up in Carrington
to the body of the hunter
they killed.
- Poor guy.
- Teresa, hey.
Hey, Sarah. Thanks for coming by.
I wanted you to meet Miss McVie
before we made a decision
about the charges against her.
This is Juliana
and her brother Noah.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Sarah works at the D.A.'s office.
She just had a baby boy
last year.
Yes, I did.
Lisbon, do you want to...
And I was gonna tell them
that their brother died
because he was going
to do the right thing.
He's kind of a hero.
Well, yeah, I guess
you could say that.
And I was gonna say that given
the extenuating circumstances
that maybe the CBI
and the D.A.'s office
would consider dropping
the charges against Juliana.
Because it's the right
thing to do.
Yes. Okay.
Nicely played, Teresa.
You owe me one.
Good to meet you,
Juliana, Noah.
- Charges dropped.
- I see what you did there.
- Thank you. I-I really appreciate it.
- No problem.
Oh. Wait.
These are yours now.
Thank you.
You're welcome.